Guide to the Seychelles Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Seychelles collection
1938-2013
1957-1995
MS 1540
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.52
(3 boxes)
The collection consists of printed material relating to political conditions in Seychelles.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Tranferred from the African Collection Curator.
Associated Materials
African Collection (MS 605); African Postcard Collection (MS 1575). Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library.
Arrangement
The material in the original accession is arranged chronologically. Additions to the collection may vary in arrangement.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of printed material relating to political conditions in Seychelles.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Seychelles -- Politics and government
- Inventory, 1977-1993
  - Rene, France Albert: presidential address, 1977 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Seychelles People's Progressive Front (SPPF): policy statement, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Peace Corps: newsletter, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Solda le Pep: Magazine of Information and Education of the People's Defence Forces, 1982, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Seychelles Agence Presse (SAP): newsletters, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Démocratie Athénienne, Institut Seychellois pour la Démocratie, 1993 May (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Additional Material, Accession 1997-M-172
  - Additional printed materials, 1938, 1959-1979, 1987, 1993-1995, undated (Box 1)
- Additional material, 1973-2013; Accession 2015-M-001
  - Printed material, 1973-2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)